yeechat.com 2013-12-06

# TopCMM Software Ltd.- Leading Chat Software Provider since 2003 - support

## Privacy Statement For TOPCMM Software Ltd.

TOPCMM is committed to protecting your privacy when you use websites, products and service. In this policy we explain how and why we collect your information, what we do with it and what controls you have over our use of it.

From time to time, we add or change functions, features or products to our Web Sites or add or change Products and Services. This, and our commitment to protecting the privacy of your personal information, may result in periodic changes to this Privacy Policy. As a result, please remember to refer back to this Privacy Policy regularly to review any amendments. 

Any questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed to contact at TOPCMM at support@123flashchat.com.

### Your acceptance of these Privacy Statement terms

By using any of the sites within our web site network ("Web Sites") or our Services, you unconditionally agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

### What data do we collect and how do we use it?

TOPCMM collects and processes information about you in order to:

(i) identify you each time you visit a Web Site, trial use the Products or wish to have a Service provided;   
(ii) process orders or applications submitted by you via shareit.com or paypal;   
(iii) Optimize our Services and Web Sites   
(iv) Get to know how long and how frequent you have stayed on the specific webpages to offer you instant assistance if needed;   
(v) carry out research on the demographics, interests and behavior of all of our customers;   
(vi) send information to you if you have subscribed to the maillist, including information about new TOPCMM products and services.

You may be asked, either when you apply chat hosting service with us, or when you chat with our sales rep. in the online chat demo or at other times, for information about yourself, such as your name, e-mail address and website address, etc. In addition, when you order products or services from our agents Shareit.com or Paypal.com, you may need to offer your financial details to them to process the order. But we TOPCMM will never need to know your credit/payment card number and expiration date. 

### Log files/IP addresses

When you visit our Web Sites, chat in online Demo room, or place order, we automatically log your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically recognized by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer our Web Sites and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.

### Non personal information

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the refer site from which you linked to our Web Sites. You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on our Web Sites. 

### Use of Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a Web Site transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. Your experience at our Web site won’t be Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web. Although they do identify a user's computer, cookies do not personally identify customers or passwords. Credit card information is not stored in cookies.

### With whom is the information shared?

TOPCMM will not share, sell or rent your personal information to third parties. 

TOPCMM may disclose aggregate statistics about our sales, our Web Site visitors and customers in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, investors and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

TOPCMM may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of TOPCMM and its Web Sites, visitors to the Web Sites and customers of our Services.

Our Web Site contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites, we suggest that you read their privacy policies. TOPCMM is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites. 

### Information about products and services

It is very important to us that we provide you with the highest level of service. In order to help us do this, from time to time TOPCMM companies may send you details of our products and services which we think may be of interest to you. If at any time you do not wish to receive these details, please e-mail us at support@123flashchat.com so we can unsubscribe you from the maillist.

### Security

TOPCMM places a great importance on the security of all information associated with our customers. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control. For example, our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized personnel have access to user information. You will not be asked for financial details on our Web sites because all the purchases will be done via Shareit.com, paypal.com or via the bank.

### Where is the information stored?

Information which you submit via our Web Sites is stored in our database on a computer located in China. This is necessary in order to process the information and to send you any information you have requested or products you have purchased. 

### Comments

Please email any questions, concerns or comments you have about our Privacy Policy to support@123flashchat.com.
